In modern web development,
المدرب: في تطوير الويب الحديث
we typically also work with third party libraries.
، نعمل عادةً أيضًا مع مكتبات الجهات الخارجية.
We don't write all the code of our projects on our own.
نحن لا نكتب كل الكود الخاص بمشاريعنا بمفردنا.
Instead, typically we utilize third party libraries
بدلاً من ذلك ، عادةً ما نستخدم مكتبات الجهات الخارجية
so that we don't always have to reinvent the wheel
حتى لا نضطر دائمًا إلى إعادة اختراع العجلة
on our own but can add certain functionalities
بمفردنا ولكن يمكننا إضافة وظائف معينة إلى مشاريعنا
to our projects and then just focus
ثم التركيز فقط على منطق أعمالنا الأساسي.
Now, in this module, we will have a look
الآن ، في هذه الوحدة ، سنلقي
at third party libraries and how you can add them
نظرة على مكتبات الطرف الثالث وكيف يمكنك إضافتها
to your TypeScript project,
إلى مشروع TypeScript
and specifically, we'll have a look at two types
الخاص بك ، وعلى وجه التحديد ، سنلقي نظرة على نوعين
of libraries and what working with them
من المكتبات وما يعنيه العمل معهم في
in a TypeScript project means.
مشروع TypeScript .
We'll have a look at normal libraries,
سنلقي نظرة على المكتبات العادية ، والتي
which you could use in regular JavaScript projects, as well,
يمكنك استخدامها في مشاريع JavaScript العادية أيضًا
and you will learn how you can use them
، وستتعلم كيف يمكنك استخدامها في TypeScript
in TypeScript and get the most out of them,
والحصول على أقصى استفادة منها ، ولكن بعد
but then we will also have a look
ذلك سنلقي نظرة أيضًا على بعض مكتبات
at some TypeScript specific libraries.
TypeScript المحددة.
The difference will be that these are libraries
سيكون الاختلاف هو أن هذه مكتبات تستخدم
that really utilize and embrace certain types of features
حقًا أنواعًا معينة من الميزات وتتبنيها لمنحك طريقة جديدة
to give you a brand new way of working with them
تمامًا للعمل معها لمنحك وظائف
to give you certain functionalities
معينة لا يمكنك إنشاؤها مثل هذا
you can't build like this with vanilla JavaScript.
باستخدام Vanilla JavaScript.
So let's have a look at both in this module.
لذلك دعونا نلقي نظرة على كليهما في هذه الوحدة.